6/8/2016 Denis Wells

Denis Wells

deniswells59@gmail.com (209) 751-6168 www.deniswells.com

While my focus has changed a few times in my life, I've always had a strong drive for my work. I gained experience as an actor and as a team leader, but knew I hadn't committed to the correct passion quite yet. Stepping back, I noticed the constant in my life was tech and a career shift was imminent. From late night gaming as a kid, to building my own PC as a teen, I've consistently enjoyed exploring and building different technology. Since I've began my developing career, doors have flown open and I seek out every opportunity to improve. Whether that be myself, tools I use, or a project I'm working on.

Twitter @deniswells59 LinkedIn deniswells qithub deniswells59

SKILLS

WEB DEVELOPMENT	HTML, CSS, Javascript, MEAN Stack
BACKEND	Node, express, Mongo, MySQL, SQLite
FRONTEND	jQuery, React, SASS, Bootstrap, Materialize
MOBILE	Ionic, Responsive Design

EXPERIENCE

Costco Wholesale

Supervisor Oct 2014 – Apr 2016

Working for a large company requires a stand-out work ethic to achieve promotions consistently. Organizing the day's work and rectifying the process of each task was my primary motivation. This, combined with creating great customer service experiences, allowed for me to stand out to my superiors.

- Increased production by discovering more efficient ways to complete daily tasks
- Ensured that every goal was met by personally committing to the compeletion
- Improved morale by rehabilitating a dysfunctional team, while simultaneously introducing new management

6/8/2016 Denis Wells

Costco Wholesale

Frontend Clerk Oct 2012 – Apr 2014

- Examined the company's needs at scale and worked with management to better myself
- Brought new ideas to the forefront, leading to my eventual promotion

EDUCATION

Coding House

Apr 2016 – Jul 2016 Javascript – Web Development

- Full Stack Javascript
- 14 week Coding Bootcamp
- 70+ hours and 2-3 apps a week

AWARDS

Actor of the Year

May 2010 High School Peers

Dedication to my academic work as well my art was recognized by instructors and surrounding peers

Actor of the Year

May 2011 High School Peers

First recipient to be awarded for two consecutive years